

CONTACT DETAILS

- +91 8668147126
- 🤊 Pollachi, Tamilnadu

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- Figma
- HTML & CSS
- Bootstrap
- Javascript
- Routing
- Switching

PERSONAL SKILLS

- Quick Learning
- Presentation abilities
- Collaboration with Team
- Creativity & Problem-solving
- · Decision making
- Time management

BIO

- Marital Status Single
- Father Name M.Sivaraj
- DOB March 4, 1999
- Willing to Relocate Anywhere
- Language Known- Tamil & English

MATHANKUMAR.S

FRONTEND WEB DEVELOPER

SUMMARY

Currently pursuing a **Certification on Full Stack Web Development** Course and also Working professionally as a Technical Support Engineer in ACT Fiber-net and having overall experience of 3 Years. Now I'm looking forward to changing my career path as a Web Developer where I can enhance my skills and gain experience and knowledge.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Technical Support Engineer Atria Convergence Technologies | Oct 2020 - Present

Roles and Responsibilities:

- Handling tickets and helping out clients to get resolve with their internet-related problems and router related issues.
- Handling static IP activation & deactivation and providing solutions to all the IP related routing issues.
- Helping out for VPN related issues and pinging issues throughout multiple Servers.

Technical Support Engineer Bharti Airtel (Teamlease) | Sep 2020 - Oct 2022 | 2 Years

Roles and Responsibilities:

- Helping clients to configure modem and mesh router over the voice call; handling all browsing-related issues.
- Handling port forwarding, telnet issues and port-related problems
- Maintaining 100% SLA. → Having good knowledge of handling Airtel customized tools like ICRM, HNV, and TMS-1000.

EDUCATIONAL HISTORY

Sree Saraswathi Thyagaraja College of Arts and Science | Bharathiar University

• B.Sc Computer Science | June 2016 - May 2019 Passed out with a 61% of score.

Oxford Matriculation Higher Secondary School

- HSC Passed out with 65% of the score.
- SSLC Passed out with 85% of the score.

COLLEGE PROJECTS

Designed Software to Digitize the Company Records

Using Visual Basic.Net, developed a software to digitize the company records for Mushroom Exports and Imports Pvt Ltd,